{
  "Player": {
    "question": "Picks for: ",
    "answers": ["Bob", "Jacob","Zach"],
    "followups": {
      "Bob": {
        "Week num":{
          "question":"Week num",
          "answers":[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16]
        },
        "ACC": {
          "question": "ACC",
          "answers": ["FSU", "Clemson"]
        },
        "Big 10":{
            "question":"Big 10",
            "answers":["Ohio State","Michigan"]
        },
        "Big 12":{
            "question":"Big 12",
            "answers":["TCU","Kansas"]
        },
        "SEC":{
            "question":"SEC",
            "answers":["Alabama","Georgia"]
        },
        "P4 Flex":{
            "question":"P4 Flex",
            "answers":["Ohio State","Michigan"]
        },
        "American":{
            "question":"American",
            "answers":["Memphis","ECU"]
        },
        "C-USA":{
            "question":"C-USA",
            "answers":["FIU","MTSU"]
        },
        "MAC":{
            "question":"MAC",
            "answers":["Bowling Green","Akron"]
        },
        "Mountain West":{
            "question":"Mountain West",
            "answers":["Air Force","Colorado State"]
        },
        "Sun Belt":{
            "question":"Sun Belt",
            "answers":["App State","Coastal Carolina"]
        },
        "G5 Flex":{
            "question":"G5 Flex",
            "answers":["Team 1","Team 2"]
        },
        "Wild Card":{
            "question":"Wild Card",
            "answers":["Team 1","Team 2"]
        },
      },
      "Jacob": {
        "Week num":{
          "question":"Week num",
          "answers":[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16]
        },
        "ACC": {
          "question": "ACC",
          "answers": ["FSU", "Clemson"]
        },
        "Big 10":{
            "question":"Big 10",
            "answers":["Ohio State","Michigan"]
        },
        "Big 12":{
            "question":"Big 12",
            "answers":["TCU","Kansas"]
        },
        "SEC":{
            "question":"SEC",
            "answers":["Alabama","Georgia"]
        },
        "P4 Flex":{
            "question":"P4 Flex",
            "answers":["Ohio State","Michigan"]
        },
        "American":{
            "question":"American",
            "answers":["Memphis","ECU"]
        },
        "C-USA":{
            "question":"C-USA",
            "answers":["FIU","MTSU"]
        },
        "MAC":{
            "question":"MAC",
            "answers":["Bowling Green","Akron"]
        },
        "Mountain West":{
            "question":"Mountain West",
            "answers":["Air Force","Colorado State"]
        },
        "Sun Belt":{
            "question":"Sun Belt",
            "answers":["App State","Coastal Carolina"]
        },
        "G5 Flex":{
            "question":"G5 Flex",
            "answers":["Team 1","Team 2"]
        },
        "Wild Card":{
            "question":"Wild Card",
            "answers":["Team 1","Team 2"]
        },
      },
      "Zach": {
        "Week num":{
          "question":"Week num",
          "answers":[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16]
        },
        "ACC": {
          "question": "ACC",
          "answers": ["FSU", "Clemson"]
        },
        "Big 10":{
            "question":"Big 10",
            "answers":["Ohio State","Michigan"]
        },
        "Big 12":{
            "question":"Big 12",
            "answers":["TCU","Kansas"]
        },
        "SEC":{
            "question":"SEC",
            "answers":["Alabama","Georgia"]
        },
        "P4 Flex":{
            "question":"P4 Flex",
            "answers":["Ohio State","Michigan"]
        },
        "American":{
            "question":"American",
            "answers":["Memphis","ECU"]
        },
        "C-USA":{
            "question":"C-USA",
            "answers":["FIU","MTSU"]
        },
        "MAC":{
            "question":"MAC",
            "answers":["Bowling Green","Akron"]
        },
        "Mountain West":{
            "question":"Mountain West",
            "answers":["Air Force","Colorado State"]
        },
        "Sun Belt":{
            "question":"Sun Belt",
            "answers":["App State","Coastal Carolina"]
        },
        "G5 Flex":{
            "question":"G5 Flex",
            "answers":["Team 1","Team 2"]
        },
        "Wild Card":{
            "question":"Wild Card",
            "answers":["Team 1","Team 2"]
        },
      },
    }
}
}
